Episode 1 Go get him, Zoro!
What are you waiting for?
Punch him out!
Knock him on the floor!
You can't - I don't need a cheering squad!
Go hide somewhere!
All right, you guys.
Do you think you could make
this a little challenging?
Come on, Saru!
This is why we keep you around!
It's the only thing you can do, Al, right?
Hurry up and finish off those
ugly-looking, really bad, evil people!
What do you think you're doing?
Hold up!
Primary rule to assassination says all
weaker targets are to be eliminated first.
We'll show you how professionals
handle these sorts of things.
What, you mean me?
Hold on just a minute.
Getting rid of me won't
accomplish anything at all.
Sure, I'm pretty and I know
how to dress, but that's it.
I really don't have any fighting skills.
Yes, we know.
It's fairly obvious.
As we said, picking off the weak ones
first is the fastest way to work.
Ah, and that's exactly why I told
her to shut up and hide somewhere.
Destiny, fate, dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
It's hard to look away, even
though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you, oh, oh!
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
Live how we want to.
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Luffy dead? Impossible!
I don't believe you!
Nonetheless, it's true.
Poor Straw Hat, buried
in the sands of Rainbase.
Dear Miss Wednesday.
If only he hadn't gotten
involved with you?
He might have lived a long and happy life.
You're a liar!
He couldn't be killed by the likes of you!
You know, it's only
because of his sacrifice.
That you're still alive to
Raven Rant at this moment!
You owe him your deepest thanks.
That way, maybe he'll
at least be able to...
Tell me where he is!
Did you come here just to torture me?
Be able to rest in peace.
That brainless little fool, when did
she manage to lose herself this time?
This is why I told her to
pipe down and hide. But no,
she has to go running off on her own
and make me waste time looking for her,
stupid Nami.
That's it, I can't run anymore.
I'll have to fight!
Like hell!
This is taking too long.
So hasty.
Zoro!
That stone column just split into pieces.
It didn't split.
It was sliced.
Only a swordsman could have
done something like that.
That's right.
You cut it, didn't you?
With those arms, huh?
You've got a rather
unusual body, don't you?
You noticed.
I ate the dice-dice fruit
making blades of my entire body.
You're him.
The swordsman who supposedly cut
down a hundred men at Whiskey Peak.
He's also the pirate who
turned down an invitation
to join Baroque work several
years ago at East Blue.
And cut down on Mr. Seven at the time.
That was you too?
You?
That's a story that takes me back.
That little misunderstanding was your Mr.
Seven's fault for not accepting
the terms I offered him.
As I remember it, I made a
very generous proposition.
I said, sure, I'll join as
long as you make me your boss.
You're quite a comedian, aren't you?
Instead of meeting my terms, he
rather rudely took a slash at me,
so naturally I put him in his place.
Now, would you like to invite me to because
right now you guys look so ridiculous.
I wouldn't even accept the job
You think you can make a fool out of me?
You some swordsman from
an upstart pirate crew?
Maybe I am but what do
you think you guys are?
Puppets with no will of your own being
manipulated by crocodile into building his
fake utopia or maybe you're all just
little tin soldiers
all shine and no steel?
Miss double finger I know I know
you want to eliminate him don't you?
You do as you please I'll
take care of the girl.
Oh, Nami, be careful.
Okay, she's gone.
I guess her plan must have failed.
She wasn't able to stop the
rebel army at the entrance.
I wonder if Vivi and the
others are all right.
They're all fighting, putting
their lives on the line.
And here I am, running and hiding.
You heard me!
I need help!
I want you to build me a weapon!
Build you a weapon?
And what are you gonna do
with it, hide behind it?
Dash.
Okay, so I'm not a warrior.
I'm just really cute with
a great figure. Say what?
But even so,
I at least want to be strong
enough not to endanger the others.
Especially this time, for Vivi.
Hmm?
Usopp, I know you understand how I feel.
We're not like the others.
They're all as strong as monsters.
In a fight, they can rely on their
own power to defeat almost any enemy.
But us, we're just a couple of ordinary
humans with no special abilities.
When a battle starts, you
and I are just in the way.
We're a burden to the others.
We can't even protect ourselves.
If we're going to fight
beside them, we need weapons.
Really powerful ones. Or else...
Isn't that the reason you're
always inventing new weapons?
So you'll be able to hold your own
in a battle with them without shame?
Am I right?
It's the same for me.
To help Vivi.
I want to fight with my own two hands.
Will you help me or not?
We don't have much time
left till we reach Alabasta.
You're right.
I guess you can't turn me
into a warrior overnight.
Sorry for being so unreasonable.
Unreasonable maybe, but
it's not impossible.
Hey, were you suggesting there's
something the mighty Usopp can't do?
Yeah?
Does that mean you're
really going to do it?
I love you!
Thank you, Usopp!
Now, as to the matter of the
cost, this won't be cheap!
I really, really mean it!
Thank you!
Yeah, we covered the gratitude part.
But top-of-the-line weapons aren't free!
I'm counting on you, Kay!
Hold on a minute!
Relax, boys.
You're off the hook.
What am
I
doing?
I'm jumping at noises now.
And after I shot my mouth off in front
of Usopp like that, I'm ready, aren't I?
To fight for VD?
After all, Usopp kept his promise.
Okay, I'll fight!
If it's just that one
woman I should be able to?
Give it up, girl.
It's useless.
Miss Doublefinger.
But what was that
spear-like weapon she used?
Does she have Devil Fruit powers, too?
I know what you're thinking.
You're right.
I ate the Spike Spike Fruit.
It granted me the power to release
spikes from anywhere on my body.
Spikes that can pierce right
through a solid stone wall.
If I slip up just once, she'll
make a pincushion out of me,
and that'll be the end of the story.
What?
Don't tell me you're actually
going to try and fight me.
Yes?
It can call upon clouds.
It can summon forth the rain.
It can create the wind itself.
My marvelous invention can cause disaster.
with its elemental power!
Stay away, or feel the
force of my climb-a-tact!
Climb-a?
What now?
For sunny weather, find take the world!
Wow, look at that!
It made dubs appear!
Dump thing!
Are you alright?
Okay, that was just the first try.
Besides, now we've gotten
her to lower her guard.
Very clever, Usopp.
This time you've hacked!
Cloudy Timbal!
And now we've got some pretty flowers!
Piece of junk!
Hmm.
I don't know her story,
but what a poor kid.
Try again!
Save the princess!
Cannons!
Bring cannons in!
Destroy the gates! Bury!
D .A .C. says flute!
What the?
Maybe now we can have a
little peace and quiet.
What a stubborn girl.
You're just wasting your time
dodging my attacks, you know?
You haven't got a chance.
I do too.
These instructions say there
are tons more attacks now.
Be a good girl and stay
right where you are.
That way I'll be able to kill you
without causing you too much pain.
Oh?
Does this.
This show of yours has a second act.
Forecast thunder!
Thunder Tempo!
Thunder Tempo.
Thunder Tempo. Thunder... Finger!
Stinger!
My cheek is bleeding.
Am I going to die like this?
I am, Marta.
I'm going to die.
And I'll haunt him!
Long-nosed fool!
Long-nosed...
Why didn't he make a real weapon?
What's this?
So, I'll kill you now. Okay?
How is she doing that?
And why?
Hedgehog! Stay there!
Too close!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait! Hold on!
Listen, hold on!
Just a minute!
Can't you give a girl a minute?
I'm not ready yet!
Come on!
Ceasefire!
No fair timeouts! Stop!
I can't stay out in the open like this!
This is it!
Time for you to get skewered!
No! Thank you!
Well, it looks like she's got a little
more battle experience than I thought.
Not that it'll help. Where was it?
I saw it.
There was something that looked useful
somewhere in these
climate-hacked instructions.
Damn it, where?
That's it.
Next time you're at a
party and things are slow,
just use these little tricks I've written
up, and things will really start to jump.
People will love them!
I'll kill you!
Oh, by the way, I've jotted down a
few battle configurations on the back.
On the back?
Let's see.
Where could you be hiding
yourself this time?
Little kitty
I'm through running and hiding.
I may not look it, but during
my eight years as a thief,
I survived all kinds of
crises, all by myself.
You can't treat me like
some ordinary girl now!
Bring it on, hussy!
Kitty found her claws.
Well then, show me what you've got.
You've got it!
Taste my real power!
The battle configurations of the Climatat.
First, understand the
characteristics of each section.
Each one can shoot off air bubbles,
either by shaking or blowing.
The first shoots hot air.
Heat ball!
What's this? It's warm.
Next shoots cool air.
Cool ball!
Ah, how pleasant.
The last shoots electricity!
Thunder ball!
Oh my, that tingled.
Of course these techniques
aren't quite finished yet?
So if you use them at parties,
you need to be careful.
Then why write them down?
Look, are we done here?
Sewing Stinger!
Please, please!
Something I can use for
battle, not for party!
Some real technique,
something I can fight with!
I'm sorry, girl.
But I've had enough of these games.
Stinger, step!
I see.
The heat ball and cool ball join together.
When they stop spinning, the bubbles
hit each other, creating an airflow,
generating a powerful wind.
Brilliant, Usopp.
The cyclone tempo is like
an ordinary boomerang,
so if you take it outside after the party
to play with, you have to watch out.
He really doesn't get it.
But let's see here. Maybe I...
What kind of weapon is that?
Don't you dare turn your back on me!
To turn your back to your enemy
in the middle of a battle.
You didn't value your life too highly.
I changed the air density
by using a cool ball.
The temperature difference caused
a refraction of light known as...
A mirage.
No way.
At this distance?
We can't win with power.
If we're gonna survive,
we gotta use our brains.
That's how we fight, right?
Used properly, this can make miracles.
I'd say this is the perfect weapon for me.
Okay, Spiky, I'm ready.
Now why don't you give up?
Well, well, you're alive.
Oh, man! Sanji!
You're hurt.
So, does this mean that you beat up Mr.
Two?
Better believe it.
Here.
My goggles!
So you got them back for
me from that creep, huh?
Thank you, Sanji.
Oh, you're the best.
Wait a minute.
They're broken!
In that case, I take
back everything I said!
Thanks for nothing, you jerk!
And they were the latest bottles, too!
Do you have any idea what I
had to do to get these things?
Hey, look at that.
Look at my poor goggles! Whoa.
That must be the auxiliary
force for the rebel army.
There's more of them?
Looks like it.
I guess Phoebe wasn't able
to stop the fighting in time.
This is just great.
What the hell?
Hey, Eyelash, it's about
time you showed up.
Where have you been hiding?
Let's hurry to the palace.
Maybe there's still a way
we can help Phoebe out.
Come on. Wait.
Usopp, move it.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Hey, Eyelash, give me a lift. Wait, stop.
Don't you see the bandages?
Help a ninja man out, will ya?
No, father!
Let the king go, crocodile. At once!
Phoebe, I'm sorry.
I failed you.
And the nation.
I didn't use the chance you
risked your life for. Oh, father.
Let me tell you a little something.
I have no intention of keeping
you or your father alive.
When a kingdom dies out,
it only seems natural its royal
family should die out as well.
But first, before I take the throne,
there's something I need to ask the current
king, if you have a moment, that is.
In fact, this has been my
goal from the very beginning.
Cobra, tell me, where's the Pluton?
Oh, Ken, you know that name.